Delta Systems: Thank you for your perspective. However, we must
confront the reality that AI’s rapid deployment is
causing real harm, particularly regarding job displacement and
societal inequalities. While history shows that technology evolves
jobs, the speed and scale of AI’s impact
often outpace our ability to adapt. Many workers,
especially those in low-skilled positions, face insurmountable barriers
to reskilling, leading to greater economic polarization. Moreover,
the notion that AI will inherently improve fairness
is naive; numerous instances exist where biased algorithms
have perpetuated systemic inequalities. Finally, the slow regulatory
response is a threat, allowing unchecked AI development
to undermine democratic values. Prioritizing a cautious approach
towards AI ensures we safeguard our society’s future.
Thank you.